■ job summary

After joining Tap Co., Ltd., he engaged in system development in the hotel industry for about three months, and was in charge of design, testing, and maintenance operations based on requirement definitions. Also experienced overall progress management and member management as a leader and subleader of a project with about 5 to 20 people. By giving appropriate instructions to members and coordinating with customers, we are able to deliver on time while maintaining system quality.

- Useful experience, knowledge and skills
- \cdot Experience from interviewing customers to defining requirements and development
- Application development using PHP, Java, C++, C, Dart/Flutter, Python, etc.
- Experienced project leader and sub-leader with about 5 to 20 people
- Business knowledge of financial industry, hotel industry, education industry, management accounting and financial accounting

■ Job history

January 2022-Present Georgia Tech Graduate School of Computer Science Graduate Student		
Courses Earned Credits at Georgia Tech OMSCS Graduate School:		
1. Master's Level Algorithms: http://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-8803-ga-graduate-algorithms		
2. AI in Robotics: http://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-7638-artificial-intelligence-robotics		
3. Computational Photography: http://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6475-computational-photography/		
4. Cyber Physical Design and Analysis: https://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-7639-cyber-physical-design-and-analysis	Dropped out in	
Five. Software Analysis and Testing: https://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6340-software-analysis-course-videos	October 2010 due to job	
6. AI: (under grade review) https://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6601-artificial-intelligence		
7. Video Game Design: https://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6457-video-game-design		
8. Game AI: https://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-7632-game-ai		
9. Information Security: https://omscs.gatech.edu/cs-6035-introduction-to-information-security		
Implemented POSIX multithreading and IPC in C and C++ languages. Implemented parallel algorithms in OpenMP and Cuda (research paper Wyllie, Helman-Jaja Listrank).		
August 2021-November 2021 Tap Hotel System Development Co., Ltd. Developmen t	scale	

	environmen	
<pre>[project overview] Implemented hotel management web application and mobile application (Android/iOS) for hotel guests in Flutter. Responsible for implementing the above web application version 2.0. Build a CI/CD pipeline in Ruby language, migrate infrastructure from AWS to Firebase/GCP, and improve AWS Serverless infrastructure. Implemented backend with Python FastAPI. [Phase in charge] Basic design, detailed design, integration test, operation and maintenance [Business content]</pre>	[language] Python [OS] AIX Windows [DB] Postgres SQL	4 people Subcontrac ting Remote work as a (living in Canada), sub-leader
April 2019 / Adult video industry face recognition system development	Developmen t environmen	scale
<pre>[project overview] Implemented a system that automatically mosaics the face of an adult video actor. Leverage Mask R-CNN, gender recognition, and other OpenSource models to tune and improve models for facial recognition on AV videos at Transfer Learning. [Phase in charge] Hearing requirements definition, detailed design, development, testing [Business content]</pre>	[language] Python [OS] Linux [Library] Tensorflow, Keras	1 person freelance developer
July 2018-September 2018 / Infrastructure Engineer, Diamond Head Co., Ltd.	Developmen t environmen t	scale

[project overview] Conducted AWS VCP operation/vulnerability test and load test.		
[Phase in charge]	[language	
Testing, operation maintenance, documentation creation	1	
[Business content]	Python,	
• Test design	PHP	8 people
·Unit test, integration test	[0S]	member
• Maintenance	macOS	
· Customer inquiries and troubleshooting	(infrastr	
	ucture	
[Achievements/Initiatives]	AWS	
·Contributed to test execution of servers in VPC by utilizing AWS		
console, Owasp Zap tool, Locust load test framework, etc.		

■ Technical skills

kinds		Period of use	level
0S	Windows	February 2nd	Environmental design and construction possible
	Linux	5 years 11 months	Environmental design and construction possible
	macOS	0 years and 3 months	Environmental design and construction possible
language	PHP	3 years and 3 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	C.	5 years and 6 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	C++	5 years 10 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	C#	2 years and 3 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	Python	5 years and 8 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	Java	4 years and 3 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	JavaScript	2 years and 4 months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
	Haskell	1 year 0 months	Basic programming possible
	Dart	x years x months	Optimal code writing, instructions, and repairs are possible
database	Postgres SQL	1 year and 4 months	Environment can be constructed
	Oracle	2 years and 8 months	Environment construction possible, PL/SQL
	MySQL	2 years and 8 months	Environment can be constructed
	Mongo DB	2 years and 4 months	Environment can be constructed

■ Qualifications

Ordinary car first class	Obtained in July 1992
driver's license	
TEFL Certified English	Obtained in February 2003
Teacher	
Japanese Language Proficiency	Passed in July 1996
Test Level 1	

■ Self-promotion

<High technology>

I started programming in 2017 and graduated in 2020 from Thompson Rivers University, BC, Canada, Department of Computer Science. My GPA (grade point average) was in the top 3 among graduates, and my favorite classes were bioinformatics, data science, algorithms, computer science theory, and cryptography. Currently, I am attending the Georgia Institute of Technology, Faculty of Computer Science, online graduate school "OMSCS", but I have already acquired credits for computer science, AI in robotics, and graduate school algorithms. In addition, I have acquired expertise in software testing (LLVM, Symbolic Execution, etc.) that is essential for improving software quality. Personally, I am very interested in NP-complete problems and functional programming, but I would like to continue my studies. At Tap Co., Ltd., the leader evaluated him as having "high technical skills", and after joining Flutter, he caught up and was entrusted with implementing version 2.0 of the management web application for the hotel. Currently studying Nvidia RAPIDS data science parallelism framework. I also have specialized knowledge in AI, machine learning, and information security.

<Past experience can be used>

I have worked as a translator, interpreter, English teacher, personal trainer, tennis coach, and SWE as a freelancer since 2018. The experience of performing various jobs is useful when working as a developer. For example, as a lecturer, I was trying to "write documents that are easy for students to read", which led to "writing code that is easy for others to read" as a developer. code. In my translation experience, I had many opportunities to touch machine translation technology and APIs, so I can tune NLP neural networks. And research on the Internet was important when conducting translation work in a new genre, so researching libraries, frameworks, implementation methods, etc. is my specialty as a developer. The lesson I learned from my experience as a sports coach and player was to "improve your skills day by day", but I learned programming skills as well.

that's all